Jeffrey Brock

- **8**01 510 7877
- @ boccobrock@gmail.com
- {} github.com/boccobrock

EDUCATION

▶ University of Utah - Bachelor of Computer Science

(2008 - 2015 Expected)

► West High School

(2002 - 2008)

SKILLS

Languages and associated frameworks that I have experience working with:

- Java Spring, Hibernate, Selenium
- C++ Boost, Ogre, Windows API
- C ffmpeg
- C# Webforms, ASP

- Javascript AngularJS, Node.js
- Ruby Rails
- PHP Zend
- DB MySQL, MongoDB

Other Tools Proficient with svn and git, and familiar with Jira and other Atlassian tools. Comfortable working with a team of developers and good at communicating with others. Experienced with Debian based Linux distributions, Windows and OSX.

Natural Languages Native: English, Fluent: Portuguese

EXPERIENCE

► Orchid Event Solutions - Software Developer

(2014 - Ongoing)

• Maintenance and developing new features for a core framework. This framework is used for registration sites for large conventions, using features I created such as localization. Used TFS and Microsoft SQL, working with a small development team.

► Xi3 Corporation - Software Developer

(2013 - 2014)

- Implemented update system with C++ sockets to a node js server. Implemented interprocess communication with sockets, and helped build framework for a 2D and 3D windows application with numerous integrations with Windows. Implemented a build server, git workflow, usage of a test case framework, use of a issue tracker and other development practices.
- ► Christopherson Business Travel Tester and Software Developer (2011 2013)
 - Responsible for developing new tools from the back end up to the front end. Made modifications to the MySQL database, and helped develop the backend Java web service that used Hibernate and Spring. Made front end tools with PHP and Javascript. Wrote Selenium tests and tested site functionality for releases.

ABOUT ME

I like doing all kinds of projects and find programming very enjoyable. I've been coding since High School, and I have experience with a wide range of languages and frameworks.

I also do my own personal projects when time permits. My code can be found on github at the address in my info section.